Glow.
I Was Reincarnated as the 7th Prince
so I Can Take My Time
Perfecting My Magical Ability 2nd Season
Episode 24: In the Light
Well, that's funny. You blocked it?
Does that mean I'm onto something here?
Which would mean I could
force you into turning good,
but those anti-symbols of
yours are still trouble.
He's worried enough that he'll likely hold
onto the anti-divine sorcery symbol.
And with how delicate divine sorcery is,
I can't try and sneak it through
by using it like an enchantment...
He can only create three
types of symbol at once.
We're here, Prince Lloyd!
Man, you're still not done yet?!
I know you're probably trying
to take him alive, but—
He is not worthy of such mercy!
You guys...!
What brought that on?!
YOINK
You seem awfully relaxed.
Have you noticed the
distortion in the singing?
While I was discussing my past with you,
my chimeras have been marching
towards the source of this song.
Shouldn't you be concerned about—
I know.
Did you honestly think I hadn't noticed?
Burble
You don't have to hold it in.
You can howl or scream if you want.
It won't get in the way.
Your voice is lovely.
We'll change the tune to match you, Shiro!
Does this really sound like
distortion to you, Guitane?!
Because if it does,
you're the one who doesn't get it!
I've got just the thing. A type of
casting I'd been thinking about.
I'm just a seventh prince.
Of all the absurdity...!
You'll want to put them
together right now, Guitane.
How can he believe that?
Symbols for earth, water, and wind elements.
If not a god,
then what else could he possibly be?!
Triple Incantation...
I can only create three types
of symbols at once... and so—
if I use them for earth, water,
and wind like he says,
I won't be able to guard
against purifying effects.
Purification
Which is why I absolutely can't
use up all my symbols.
It would result in my ultimate defeat.
If the alternative is being
"turned good" and taken alive...
I would rather choose dea—
Earth, Water, Wind.
Excalibur!
Triple Incantation:
Glacia Krystacier!
Beautiful...!
MMMMM
Well blocked, Guitane!
This is bad, Prince Lloyd!
I mean, I get it,
but you're going totally overboard!
Are you mad, Seventh Prince?!
This spell has the potential to destroy
the world, and wipe out humanity!
*View from the surface
Did the rain just turn into a blizzard?!
Mom, look! The sky looks nasty!
It's the wrath of God!
The only person who could do this, etc...
The only person who could manage this...
Oh, come on! After all this time,
you're calling me a prince?
I thought I was a god!
There are no gods like you!
God is—
Do I still... hold these expectations...
of God?
Shiro!
I'm sorry we were late!
What do you think you're doing?
I thought you were on Guitane's side.
I'm not sure why you're here, either.
Who exactly is Bishop Guitane fighting?
It's gotta be god. Who else?
The almighty having to step in
to stop a friend's rampage...
The world could end, and I
wouldn't have a leg to stand on.
I agree. It's so very... frustrating.
I'm so glad you're okay
Let's all eat pancakes together
These lyrics are bizarre!
She's just freestyling now!
True! But it's still invigorating!
Is a pure heart enough to allow anything?!
What would that mean?! Inconsistency?!
Or divine truth?!
Then look upon me, God!
I have broken so many taboos,
become a beast...
Exploited the doubts of others,
betrayed my friends,
and embroiled an innocent like Anastasia!
Just like her savage of a father!
Look how far I have come,
propelled by the purity of my rage!
Well?! What do you say?!
O God... why?
Why don't you appear to judge me?
How long will you let this continue?!
Enough is enough!
Poke
Then what about him, then?
Will you allow this?!
Cool
The world is on the verge of being
destroyed at the hands of an "innocent"!
Surely such innocence is only being
unaware of one's own wickedness!
This isn't...
the sort of thing that can be allowed!
It isn't worth protecting!
Not a piece of it... holds any value!
Dad!
Mom, Dad's back!
Oh, you didn't get lost on your way today?
Mom, can I sing with Dad?
Okay, why don't we all sing together, then?
Dear God...
This isn't fair.
I shouldn't... Your dad's an awful singer.
Does it hurt, where you are? Are you lonely?
These days where, in my pure
desire to deny purity...
were time I spent rejecting my past,
when I felt the purest happiness.
You're so weird, Dad.
It's okay if you're bad!
Looks like dad's tired!
Yeah!
I'm gonna get him!
This willingness to come right at me...
You really are humoring me
to the very end, aren't you?
Seventh Prince!
Luma Maxima!
Even being struck by my Luma Maxima...
has no effect on him.
Luma Maxima!
It's warm.
This snow is healing my wounds!
The inversion of a divine calamity...
Is it even possible?
Purification on this scale...
It's raining again.
It follows me around, you see.
Maybe it's the heavens crying.
Unlikely.
I tend to think of it as being spat on.
I doubt the heavens will smile
upon me until my day of death.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
I looked away the entire time...
blaming god...
Taking advantage of your kindness...
If I hadn't been there... if I had
been able to stop my father...
Maybe the rain was falling
on me, all along...
Damn it, this is what I
hate about purification.
People just can't keep stuff
to themselves when it hits...
Haugh
Sorry for not noticing, kid.
It's over, isn't it, Lloyd?
Super Confession Time, Brought to you by Purification
Mommy! I'm sorry I didn't eat all my dinner.
I'm sorry I drew on the wall, too.
I should apologize for
breaking Daddy's vase, too.
Well, I guess it's fine!
I'm still unsure...
Whether or not the
purification affected you,
There, there, there.
or if this is what you were
really like, all along.
You could've forced the other archbishops
to go along with your plan if you'd wanted.
So, why didn't you?
This Great Advent Festival...
If God did not descend,
I expected them to bare their
fangs at me, in His place.
The ultimate arbiters of justice
that I personally selected.
Should I overcome them...
or if they had defeated me...
That would have been the
point of the battle.
It needed to be in earnest...
For both sides to see their
ideals through to the end.
And even then...
there were those who did not deny me.
He's so dang serious...
In the end... the ones who stopped me
was neither God, nor the bishops,
but a seventh prince and a simple nun.
I'm sure that the gods must
have blessed her voice.
Guess what, Guitane?
Wanna know why Escher became a nun?
Because I like singing.
I-I mean, I respect God and everything, too!
But since singing is the
only thing I'm good at...
the church seemed like the best place
to sing in front of a lot of people.
And that's why you joined the clergy?
B-But this Great Advent Festival
is different from the usual!
Because it's revenge!
Against that mean pastor!
Your singing
is barfaroonie...
Your singing is barfaroonie.
Barf barf spew... Spew spew hurl...
And if he's going to show up,
then I can't run away!
Hilarious, right?
It's not even vaguely religious.
Maybe instead of worrying about what's
wrong and right all the time,
for once, you could think
about what would be more fun?
I've spent my entire life living that way!
I doubt anyone else could
get away with that.
I mean, it killed me already.
Once, in my past life, living like that.
Just something I found.
In the end... what did he say to you?
I don't remember.
I'll be waiting at Lordost Island, Guitane.
The news shook Saloum.
The Pope, Guitane, was murdered as part
of a large-scale terrorist attack
by an unidentified group.
His body was discovered in one of
their subterranean laboratories.
A man disguised as the Pope
infiltrated the Great Advent Festival,
acting as the mastermind
behind the incident.
Was the motive some kind of
rebellion against the gods?
The mysterious perpetrator's
whereabouts remain unaccounted for.
This is so irritating!
Their whereabouts are "unaccounted for"?!
It was Pope Guitane who did it all!
Give it a rest, Rozelis.
There are bishops who don't know the truth.
We just need to keep our traps shut.
Especially with how this could
affect the Church's reputation.
If people start to question
divine teachings...
it could destroy the peace
this nation enjoys.
Well, we can't leave things as-is anyway!
The church needs a new
leader to guide its flock!
That being the case, I humbly
accept the position of pope!
That ain't happening.
There's someone better I have in mind.
Someone with overwhelming public
support and charisma to boot.
Excuse me?
Please, undertake the trial to become pope!
Who are you asking?
You!
Why?
Because we want you to be the pope!
Huhhhh?!
Huuuh?!
My little brother sometimes
appears in my room.
The fact that I won't tell anyone
is probably convenient, for him.
Sorry. I did knock, but you were
having such a good time playing...
I'm leaving...
Lloyd. You called it, back at the church.
There's likely to be a major attack
at the Great Advent Festival.
When that happens, I believe
that the two of you
continuing the recital will have
a major effect on the outcome.
I'd like you to start playing when you feel
like the town has become too loud to bear.
I'll arrange the stage for you.
Why?
Why tell only me all this?
Because...
If I told anyone else, they'd put a
stop to it, because of the danger.
That's true.
Heretics.
What did you think?
Did the performance live up to your hopes?
We both know who we are.
And that there are things we'd die for.
Yes! It was the best recital ever!
Subjects of obsession that we
pursue to the point of heresy.
You worked hard too, huh, Shiro?
You're a good boy! And a strong boy!
You did well, too.
Spell notation?!
She took my incantations...
Even if she's only using tones,
she was able to mimic them by ear?!
Did you... happen to hear me,
up above the clouds...?
I mean, I was hiding the whole time!
I don't recognize any of this weird stuff!
Lloyd.
The Great Advent Festival
was fun, wasn't it?
There's no need for any questions.
Just like he won't get in my way,
I don't intend on getting in his.
No one can stop either of us.
And I love these moments where we,
as heretics, can spend time together.
Where's the women's bath?!
BOM BOM BOM
Lordost Island's newest attraction is perfect
Why?! Why?!
for washing away both mental
and physical exhaustion!
And the only person allowed to bathe co-ed
at Seven Wolf Springs is Prince Lloyd!
No peeking allowed!
Becoming the pope...
The spiritual leader of the people...
I really don't think I can handle it.
It's definitely a major responsibility.
But it's amazing! I mean, becoming pope?!
Sounds dumb to me!
You won't have time to see the
guy you like, if that happens.
What did Babylon say, anyway?
Just, "I see."
Wait, why would you bring him up?!
I'd be sad if I couldn't
see Lloyd anymore, too.
Talk about bittersweet!
Then you've got Sylpha and Ren who are
both head over heels for Lloyd...
I-I-I never said that!
And you took part in that contest
for a date with him, too, Tao!
I was just doing that to mess with you two!
Sylpha.
Can I go now?
You can not.
Wh-Wh-What is Lloyd doing in here?!
This happened before, didn't it?
Lloyd! At this rate,
they're gonna make me the pope!
What should I do?!
An expression like
he's looking at a bug
I see.
If you're going to be that cold about
it, I'll nominate your for pope!
H-How'd you get that idea?!
Prince Albert was bragging to Bishop Dante
about how you helped resolve this
incident with your brilliant deductions!
My little brother's an ace detective!
He's the second
candidate for Pope.
That stupid brother...!
I'm afraid not! Prince Lloyd is going to
live peacefully at the castle, with me!
He is not going to be put
on display for the world!
On display?!
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
It means being put on display...?
That sounds right up your alley, Escher.
Being on display.
Saria?
That's not me. It's a rock.
Do you remember...
that time I played a
recital at the church...?
Please let me sing with you!
No.
Let me sing with you!
How you chased after me for days,
demanding we perform a duet?
I just... really wanted
to sing with your music.
There are so many guests
for your recitals, Saria.
And if I was able to make those
people happy with my singing...
I'd just be so thrilled.
Are you saying you intend to use the
church and myself as a platform?
Oh, no! Not at all!
It won't just be a lot of people.
Your singing would be heard...
around the world.
If you use the platform of being the pope.
Saria...
That's not me. It's a duckie.
That's true. She's exactly right.
Everyone will be listening...
to my song!